carolinanightlife.com 2013-05-23

# Our Privacy Policy - Carolina Nightlife Presented by Corona Extra

Privacy Policy

Effective: June 30th, 2009

Thank you for visiting our website. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and services.

Your privacy is important to us at CarolinaNightlife.com. We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our website. We want you to feel confident and secure in using our services and to understand we take the privacy of your personal information very seriously. We will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. CarolinaNightlife.com will be referred to as "we", "us", and "our" and visitors to the site we will refer to as "you" and "your".

This privacy policy tells how we will use personal information collected at this site. By using the site you are accepting the practices described in the privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.

We want you to understand:

1\. What information is gathered?

2\. How the information is collected.

3\. How the information is used.

4\. Security procedures in place.

5\. Copyrights and Trademarks

6\. No warranties.

7\. Distribution of Information

1) What Information is Gathered:

We will collect information during the membership process, including to but not limited to name, address, phone numbers, age, photos, videos and other identifiable information uploaded to the site. We may also collect non-personal information such as but not limited to IP numbers, browser types

With respect to cookies: We may use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

We collect the domain name of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, user-specific information on what pages you access or visit, information volunteered by you, such as survey information.

2) How Information is Collected:

Information that is input into an application form by you on our website, also but not limited to, questionnaires and cookies.

3) How Information is Used:

Specific information that you provide to us might be shared with third parties and advertisers to provide more relevant service and advertisement to users of this site.

4) Security Procedures In Place

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure and confidential. Only authorized personnel, (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you.

5) Copyrights and Trademarks

See Terms of Use

6) No warranties.

There are no warranties or guarantees with using this web site. You, the consumer, must, on your own opinion make decisions regarding the services offered on this website. We do not guarantee any service offered.

7) Distribution of Information

Information might be shared with third parties and advertisers to provide more relevant service and advertisement to users of this site. We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances.

RIGHT TO CHANGE PRIVACY POLICY

Our Privacy Policy is effective June 30th, 2009. CarolinaNightlife.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. By using the CarolinaNightlife.com website, you are accepting and agreeing to the terms and conditions outlined in this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect, us or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, we ask that you do not submit any personal information except in conjunction with your parents or guardian.

PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us at info@carolinanightlife.com.

www.CarolinaNightlife.com

WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THIS POLICY. EACH TIME YOU USE THIS SITE PLEASE REVIEW THIS POLICY FOR ANY CHANGES THAT MAY HAVE OCCURRED SINCE YOUR LAST VISIT.

Please print or download a copy of this agreement for your records.

Contact Us: info@carolinanightlife.com

↑ Back to top
